<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Smart Air Application</string>
    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="registration">Registration</string>
    <string name="register">Register</string>
    <string name="click_to_login">Click to Login</string>
    <string name="click_to_register">Click to Register</string>
    <string name="logout">Logout</string>
    <string name="provider_home">Provider Home</string>
    <string name="parent_home">Parent Home</string>
    <string name="child_home">Child Home</string>
    <string name="child">Child</string>
    <string name="forgot_password">Forgot Password?</string>
    <string-array name="user_roles">
        <item>Parent</item>
        <item>Provider</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="provider_welcome">
        Welcome, Provider! \n\n
        As a provider, you can view the summary reports for children, but only when a parent shares their data with you. \n\n
        You will not be able to modify or edit any of the data shared with you. \n\n
        Please wait for a parent to share an access code with you, and then submit it to see more information about the child.
    </string>
    <string name="child_welcome">
        Welcome Child! \n\n
        As a child you can log your medicines and symptoms, practice inhaler techniques, and track your asthma in a fun, safe way! \n\n

        If you’re experiencing an asthma attack, you can use the <br>Rescue</br> feature to track your symptoms and see how serious your attack is. Parents will receive an alert automatically.\n\n

        The <br>Controller</br> feature lets you check in daily to track your symptoms and medicine use, helping you stay on top of your asthma care.\n\n

        By default, only your parent can see your information. They can view summaries, check your logs, and choose what to share with your healthcare provider.\n\n

    </string>
    <string name="parent_welcome">
    Welcome, Parent!\n\n
    This app helps you support your child’s asthma care in a safe, easy way.\n\n
    - <b>See your child’s logs:</b> You can view summaries of their symptoms, medicine use, and Rescue events.\n
    - <b>Manage data sharing:</b> By default, your child’s data is private. You decide what to share with your healthcare provider. You can toggle sharing on or off at any time.\n
    - <b>Stay informed:</b> You’ll receive alerts when your child logs a Rescue, so you know if they need help.\n\n
    <b>How it works:</b>\n
    - <b>Rescue:</b> If your child is having an asthma attack, they can log their symptoms and see how serious it is. You’ll get an alert automatically.\n
    - <b>Controller:</b> Your child can check in daily to track symptoms and medicine use. You can view their logs to support their care.\n\n
    Your child’s privacy is protected, and you control what information is shared with healthcare providers.
    </string>


    <string name="confirm_password">Confirm Password</string>
    <string name="back_to_parent">Back to Parent</string>
    <string name="today_s_zone_green">Today\'s Zone: Green!</string>
    <string name="keep_up_your_routine">Keep up your routine!</string>
    <string name="pef_280_pb_310">PEF: 280 (PB: 310)</string>
    <string name="please_set_your_personal_best_pef">Please set your personal best PEF.</string>
    <string name="today_s_zone_not_set">Today\'s Zone: Not Set</string>
    <string name="today_s_zone_yellow">Today\'s Zone: Yellow!</string>
    <string name="caution_use_your_reliever_inhaler">Caution: Use your reliever inhaler.</string>
    <string name="today_s_zone_red">Today\'s Zone: Red!</string>
    <string name="danger_use_your_reliever_and_see_a_doctor">Danger: Use your reliever and see a doctor.</string>

</resources>